Revenge is Sweet.
Sweetwater is a western, thriller film directed by Logan Miller.
In the late 1800s, a fanatical religious leader, a renegade Sheriff, and a former prostitute
collide in a blood triangle on the rugged plains of the New Mexico Territory.
Sarah Ramírez, played by January Jones.
Prophet Josiah, played by Jason Isaacs.
Sheriff Cornelius Jackson, played by Ed Harris.
Miguel Ramírez, played by Eduardo Noriega.
Hugh, played by Stephen Root.
Kingfisher, played by Luce Rains.
Sweetwater (released as Sweet Vengeance in the UK, Australia and New Zealand) is a 2013 American
Western film directed by Logan Miller and co-written with Andrew McKenzie and Noah Miller.
The film stars Ed Harris, January Jones, Jason Isaacs,
Eduardo Noriega, Stephen Root and Jason Aldean.
The film explores themes of husband wife relationship, new mexico,
religious fundamentalism, lawman , religious cult.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.